<resources>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ble">Scan for BLE </string>
    <string name="title_activity_device_control">DeviceControlActivity</string>
    <string name="ble_not_supported">BLE is not supported</string>
    <string name="label_data">Data:</string>
    <string name="label_device_address">Device address:</string>
    <string name="label_state">State:</string>
    <string name="no_data">No data</string>
    <string name="connected">Connected</string>
    <string name="disconnected">Disconnected</string>
    <string name="title_devices">BLE Device Scan</string>
    <string name="error_bluetooth_not_supported">Bluetooth not supported.</string>

    <string name="unknown_device">Unknown device</string>
    <string name="unknown_characteristic">Unknown characteristic</string>
    <string name="unknown_service">Unknown service</string>

    <!-- Menu items -->
    <string name="menu_connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="menu_disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="menu_scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="menu_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="title_activity_range">RangeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nfc">NfcActivity</string>

    <string name="app_name">Beam</string>
    <string name="info">Ensure that Android Beam is enabled</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Android Beam settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_place">PlaceActivity</string>

    <!-- VIA HORSENS -->
    <string name="via_name">VIA University College</string>
    <string name="via_established">Chr M Østergaards Vej 4, 8700 Horsens</string>
    <string name="via_preview">VIA University College is one of eight new regional organizations of different
        study sites in Denmark (Danish: professionshøjskoler) offering bachelor courses of all kinds in all of
        Central Denmark Region.

        \n\nIt was established in January 2008. From January 2008 all VIA medium higher education
        in the Central Region, which previously came under CVU\'erne (Center for Higher Education).

        \n\nVIA University College is Denmark\'s third largest educational institution after Copenhagen University and
        Aarhus University. VIA has approximately 2,000 employees and 20,000 students. VIA operates within the pedagogical and social
        professional, the health professional and the technical-commercial area.</string>

    <!-- CASA ARENA HORSENS -->
    <string name="casa_name">CASA Arena Horsens</string>
    <string name="casa_established">Langmarksvej 59, 8700 Horsens</string>
    <string name="casa_preview">CASA Arena Horsens (previously Forum Horsens Arena and Horsens Idrætspark) is a Danish football stadium
        and the home ground of AC Horsens. It has a capacity between 10,400 of which 7,500 is seated.

        \n\nThe Rolling Stones were the first band to play a concert at the stadium.

        \n\nMadonna\'s concert in 2006 became the biggest concert on Horsens, with 85,232 fans in attendance.

        \n\nRecent concerts at the ground have included AC/DC in 2010 on the Black Ice World Tour, U2 in 2010 on the 360 Tour, and Bon Jovi as part
        of the 2011 European leg of The Circle Tour.

        \n\nThe company behind the reconstruction of Casa Arena Horsens is 3XN, who is also the company behind The Lighthouse in Århus, amongst many
        other large projects. In 2015 the Arena will become the third venue to host the Speedway Grand Prix of Denmark which had been previously held
        at the Vojens Speedway Center (1995-2002) and the Parken Stadium in Copenhagen (2003-2014). Moreover, the British-Irish boyband One Direction
        will visit the Arena on 16 June 2015, as a part of their On the Road Again Tour</string>

    <!-- INDUSTRIAL MUSEUM HORSENS -->
    <string name="art_name">Horsens Art Gallery</string>
    <string name="art_established">Carolinelundsvej 2, 8700 Horsens</string>
    <string name="art_preview">Welcome to Horsens Art Museum
        \n\nHorsens Art Museum is a highly profiled museum of Danish contemporary art.
        \n\nAmong a lot of other things, the museum has the biggest collection of paintings, drawings and graphic works by the famous Danish artist
        Michael Kvium, who was born and raised in Horsens.
        \n\nWith its location in the beautiful park Lunden (the Grove), Horsens Art Museum is always worth a visit.
        The building has been extended twice:  in 1992, on the initiative of the local newspaper Horsens Folkeblad. And again, in 2006, with financial
        contribution from the private foundation of Inge and Asker Larsen.
        \n\nHorsens Art Museum is build as a \‘White Cube\’ museum: Light, broadness, simplicity and harmony characterize the architecture.
    </string>

    <!-- PRISON HORSENS -->
    <string name="pri_name">Horsens Statsfængsel</string>
    <string name="pri_established">Frodesdalsvej 3, 8700 Horsens</string>
    <string name="pri_preview">The present Horsens Statsfængsel (Horsens State Prison), formerly called Horsens Straffeanstalt (Horsens Correctional
        Institution), was commissioned in 1853. Horsens was intended for prisoners serving long prison sentences. The prisoners spend the nights in
        their cells, during the day prisoners work in the prison\'s "workshops" and during the evenings, they move freely in the wards. The prison closed
        in 2006 and prisoners were moved to The State Prison of East Jutland at Enner Mark, west of Horsens. Today, the prison works as a concert venue,
        where Metallica has played.
    </string>

</resources>
